Lin, this is an awful date.
琳  这是一个糟糕的约会
I know you told me not to complain, and I'm not...
我知道你叫我别抱怨  我没抱怨
- That's just a fact. - I know.
-这是事实  -我懂
I'm not gonna say this is fun, because it's not fun, at all.
我不想说这真有意思 因为这没有意思  一点也没有
Let's just do this escape room as fast as we can,so we can go home.
那我们尽快逃出去 就可以回家了
I should text Tina real quick before that guy takes our phones away.
那家伙收手机之前我快速给蒂娜发个短信
Doing an escape room, then coming home.
正在密室逃脱  然后就回家了
Double date awful. Nightmare couple. Kill me.
四人约会太糟糕  可怕的一对  折磨我
Sad face, sad face, sad face, turd. Send.
哭脸  哭脸  哭脸  便便  发送
Okay, if everyone could surrender your phones, please.
好了  请大家把手机交给我
Oh, wait, I just got a text.
等一下  我收到一条短信
-Oh, it's from you, Linda.  -Oh, God!
-是你发来的  琳达  -天哪
Don't read that. Uh, Ruthanne..
别看  路芬
It says, "Double date awful. Nightmare couple. Kill me."
四人约会太糟糕  可怕的一对  折磨我
Sad face, sad face, sad face.
哭脸  哭脸  哭脸
- Turd. - Oh, boy.
-便便  -天